<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Big Bounty Cards</title>
        <link>https://jzfdsgn.github.io/</link>
        <description>Posts from Big Bounty Cards</description>
        <lastBuildDate>2025-06-12T05:24:06.174Z</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Postalgic</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        
        <item>
            <title>Egman’s OP11 Half Case Tourney</title>
            <link>https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/06/11/egman-s-op11-half-case-tourney/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<div style="margin: 16px 0;"><a href="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1749667292-C2CDF7C2-00.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1749667292-C2CDF7C2-00.jpg" alt="Image 1" width="100%"/></a></div>
<p>Yesterday Egman hosted his half case tourney, one of our first big OP11 events. While it’s not an official event, it’s still a good peek into the current playing field of the meta. Especially considering the sim hadn’t been updated with the new cards prior to the event.</p><p><a href="https://egmanevents.com/one-piece-op11-tournaments/half-case-tournament">Here’s the link to Egmans’s report.</a></p><p>It’s not surprising that UP Luffy and Belo Betty make up a majority of the pie chart. What is surprising is the diversity in the rest of the leaders played. And even more surprising is that Lucci won the whole event. The finals were Lucci vs. Belo Betty.</p><p>It’s notable that Lucci did not run into any Buggy’s the entire tournament, which is supposed to be a really bad matchup for the cat.</p><p>It gives me some hope to see BP Luffy with a strong showing, coming in 3rd. Not to mention there are 2 of them in the Top 8.</p><p>Now I feel even more unsure of what to play for Vegas. So I asked my buddy Claude (AI) to give me the conversion rates of each leader in the top 16. Check it out! <br><br><strong>Top 16 Leader Conversion rates</strong> <br> <iframe src="/egman-op11-half-case-tourney.html"></iframe> <br> <br><em>There’s no data on how many total players used Usopp or Newgate so their conversion rates are missing.</em> <br><br>Now I’m strongly considering BP Luffy, but that means having to buy EB02 secret luffy. I could also just play Betty since I have the deck. Decisions, decisions..</p><p>Till next time, <br>GGs</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>2025-06-11T18:36:41.829Z</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/06/11/egman-s-op11-half-case-tourney/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Road to Vegas Regional</title>
            <link>https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/06/10/road-to-vegas-regional/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<div style="margin: 16px 0;"><a href="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1749589530-F9F48DFB-00.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1749589530-F9F48DFB-00.jpg" alt="Image 1" width="100%"/></a></div>
<p>The regional in Vegas is coming up soon and I have no idea what to play.</p><p>I don’t think Marco is as good into this meta. He has a good matchup into GP and UP Luffy. But I don’t think he has a good matchup into Buggy, and the rest of the playing field is a wild card at the moment.</p><p>I haven’t had much time to practice either, but I have played a total of 7 games. 5 of those with UP Luffy and 2 with BP Luffy. All of them were against my friends Buggy.</p><p>Currently at 2 wins and 3 losses with UP Luffy. 1 win and 1 loss with BP Luffy.</p><p>I have to say, Buggy is nasty. It’s such a strong deck and fairly consistent with all the hand filtering it does. So I might consider playing him as well, but with such little time and no reps in maybe not.</p><p>Between UP and BP Luffy, UP feels way more consistent. They’re both fun, but I might just go with consistency to play it safe.</p><p>Till the next one, <br>GGs</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>2025-06-10T21:04:54.062Z</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/06/10/road-to-vegas-regional/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>OP11 Prerelease #1</title>
            <link>https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/05/31/op11-prerelease-1/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<div style="margin: 16px 0;"><a href="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1748731785-D6146261-00.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1748731785-D6146261-00.jpg" alt="Image 1" width="100%"/></a><a href="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1748731785-AA8C76CF-01.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1748731785-AA8C76CF-01.jpg" alt="Image 2" width="100%"/></a></div>
<p>I got into 2 prerelease events for this set and just got back from the first one. And I did pretty well!</p><p>Undefeated, but the store only did 3 rounds which left 4 undefeated players. Top 4 got the winner card.</p><p>Picked up a box and pulled an SP Shirahoshi! Pretty happy with that pull even though I don’t plan on using it. I’m torn on trading or selling it though since it’s such a nice looking card!</p><p>Till the next one, GGs</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>2025-05-31T22:46:45.138Z</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/05/31/op11-prerelease-1/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>OP11 Pre-releases are here!</title>
            <link>https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/05/27/op11-pre-releases-are-here/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We’re going from one flavor of purple Luffy to another with <strong>OP11: A Fist of Divine Speed.</strong></p><p>Pre-release events are starting this week, and we’re already seeing people rip some cases! This set seems to be just as polarizing as EB02 since we already know a certain purple rubber man is going to dominate the meta. But we’re also getting the new starter decks, which the east didn’t have for their OP11 meta.</p><p>I’m excited for it. I think we have a lot of players who like to cook unique decks to try and combat the meta. Not only that, we have a regional in Vegas only a few weeks into the set. Which is too soon to call it a solved meta when you consider the starter decks.</p><p>Whether you’re excited or in the OP12 waiting room, it’s always fun ripping packs. So if you’re playing in a pre-release event, I recommend this guide from <a href="https://youtube.com/@artresstcg?si=vs7LBnidoVrVHdLX">Artress</a>. He puts one out for every set.</p>
<div class="embed youtube-embed"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/unNE_c9QWho" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>]]></description>
            <pubDate>2025-05-28T04:12:59.404Z</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/05/27/op11-pre-releases-are-here/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Treasure Cup 5.24.25</title>
            <link>https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/05/26/treasure-cup-5-24-25/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<div style="margin: 16px 0;"><a href="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1748280141-73C73887-00.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://jzfdsgn.github.io/images/embeds/embed-1748280141-73C73887-00.jpg" alt="Image 1" width="100%"/></a></div>
<p>Over the weekend I played in a Store Treasure Cup with my boy Marco! I ran the animal package. I was having more success with it on the sim than the “classic” control build.</p><p>I ended up going x-1, losing in the last round to the winner. It was such a close game too. If I had played the last few turns a little differently, that we would be an X-0 up there.</p><p>Unfortunately I ended up 3rd, missing the better store credit prizing for 2nd. But overall I’m pretty happy with how I performed!</p><p><strong>Matchups</strong></p><p>r1 - ✅ RG Smoker <br>r2 - ✅ Enel <br>r3 - ✅ Rebecca <br>r4 - ✅ Lucci <br>r5 - ❌ Lucci</p><p>The funny thing is I mainly played Marco for GP Luffy but didn’t pair into any of them. There were <strong>4 Lucci’s</strong> in total. And 3 of them were in the top 4!</p><p>Till next time, <br>GG’s</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>2025-05-26T17:20:55.926Z</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jzfdsgn.github.io/2025/05/26/treasure-cup-5-24-25/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>